UI / UX Product Designer



Hard-working professional with 11+ years of experience and 6 years a proven knowledge of application development. Aiming to leverage my skills to successfully fill the UI/UX Product Designer role at your company.



Skills

- Web: HTML5, XHTML, CSS3, SCSS, JavaScript, J-Query Angular8.
- Frameworks: Twitter Bootstrap, HTML5, Sass, RWD and Developer tools of Firefox, Chrome. IE and Safari.
- Developer Tools: Dream Weaver, Visual Code, Eclipse, Brackets, etc.
- Graphics / UX : Adobe Photoshop, Adobe illustrator, Adobe XD, Figma, Invision, Apps Design, Banner Design, flyers Design, Website Template Design.



Engagement experience

I have worked as UI / UX Product Designer for clients. I was involved in interacting with the functional owners to understand the requirement and subsequently designing and developing an efficient and optimum solution for the same. I was also involved in creating viable specification and acceptance criteria for the identified solutions. Developing the solution testing strategy and plan and participating in or managing user acceptance testing.

In other engagements in my career, I was involved in coordinating with Business for the business/functional requirements, Design & Development, developing reports. I have been a part of the team in critical situations and supported, helped and shared the work. Have mingled with the team members of all cadres. I have indulged in corrective communication and achieved desired results in the deliverables of important objects.



Professional Experience

Present 2020

UI UX Product Designer / Sr. Mobile Application Developer

OpinVerse Pvt. Ltd.

In house project for Digital Marketing .OpinVerse https://opinverse.com/

https://www.figma.com/file/iU3alz5yDjg4o8xaLjw0Mt/OpinVerse Ux?node-id=0%3A1

- Understanding of whole project and create the UX Design / wireframe as well.
- Create Documentation for the development ...
- Create UI Design for Mobile app Adobe XD, Figma, illustrator, Photoshop.
- Website / Admin / CRM / Franchise Module design in Html5, Css3, Saas, Scss, Java-Script, J-Query.
- Testing, review and Architecture with Project Team.

UI / UX Product Designer

2018 - 2020 • UI / UX Product Designer

Crayonsys Technologies Pvt. Ltd.

In house project similar Like combination of Outlook and what's app . "Pipassport"

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.pipassport.passportsuite

- Understanding of whole project and create the UX Design / wireframe as well.
- Create Documentation for the development ...
- Create UI Design for Mobile app Adobe XD, Figma, illustrator, Photoshop.
- Website / Admin / CRM / Franchise Module design in Html5, Css3, Saas, Scss, Java-Script, J-Query.
- Testing, review and Architecture with Project Team.

2017 - 2018 ● UI / UX Product Designer

SAA Consultancy, UK

- 1) This project is for the UK Hospital Management Application . "TrueNorth-App"
- Understanding of whole project and create the UX Design / wireframe as well.
- Create Documentation for the development ...
- Create UI Design for Mobile app Adobe XD, Figma, illustrator, Photoshop.

2) Hospital management project for UK . "BedManagement", "BedRequest"

- Understanding of whole project and create the UX Design / wireframe as well.
- Create Documentation for the development ...
- Create UI Design for Mobile app Adobe XD, Figma, illustrator, Photoshop

2015 - 2017 ● UI / UX Product Designer

Nine One Solution

- 1) Project is for Car Marketing Company for Canada , Advertising , web and Application designing .
- Understanding of whole project and create the UX Design / wireframe as well.
- Create Documentation for the development ...
- Create UI Design for Mobile app Adobe XD, Figma, illustrator, Photoshop.
- Website / Admin / CRM / Franchise Module design in Html5, Css3 ,Saas, Scss, Java-Script , J-Query .
- Testing , review and Architecture with Project Team .

UI / UX Product Designer

- 2) The projects is for clients for Mercedes and Toyota the global Car manufacturing company. To support and offer high quality, innovative solutions as per their Requirements .
- Create Documentation for the development .
- Create UI Design for Mobile app Adobe XD, Figma, illustrator, Photoshop.
- Website / Admin / CRM / Franchise Module design in Html5, Css3 ,Saas, Scss, Java-Script , J-Query .

2014-2015 • UI / UX Product Designer

Ebunch (Canada)

- 1. The project was for High Liner Food services, It gave me an opportunity to work as a UI / UX Product Designer.
- Create Documentation for the development.
- Create UI Design for Mobile app Adobe XD, Figma, illustrator, Photoshop.
- Website / Admin / CRM / Franchise Module design in Html5, Css3 ,Saas, Scss, Java-Script , J-Query .
 - 2) Client: ADO Grupo(Spain)

Project was for ADO Grupo, I got opportunities to work on UI / UX Designing,

3) Client: Parkland Fuel Corporation(Canada)

Project for **Parkland oil Inc.** UI / UX Design and Project Documentation.

2011 - 2014 • Business Analyst

Kangaroo Software

The projects is for an Australian Client, a global IT company and software Service provider that believes in the power of Information Technologies. To support and offer high quality, innovative solutions from everyday essentials to instrument for web, Mobile application.

- Requirement gathering from the users and preparing technical specification, Develop wire-frame, Web(PHP, Wordpress) and Mobile Applications.
- Involved in the business requirements development phase, understanding the Clients requirements and providing the solutions to user requirements.
- Delivering and working along with the offshore development team of 20 members.

2008 - 2011 ● Business Analyst

Korea Link Share

UI / UX Product Designer

The projects is for a global Garments company and software Service provider that believes in the power of Information Technologies. To support and offer high quality, innovative solutions from everyday essentials to instrument for every web, every application. All from the most cited different brands. Which is based out of North America, South Korea. I have been involved in development for its Global requirements.

- Delivering and working along with the off-shore development team.
- Management and Development Activity for the package solutions project.
- Create the Technical documentation and wire frame.
- Worked on different types of web and Mobile development .



Education

University – Course / Education
JIVAJI UNIVERCITY Gwalior – B.Sc Computer Science (2006)



Contacts



+91-9617332777



asaxena2@outlook.com aamitsaxenaa1@gmail.com

Recognition: Successfully Completed End to end Implementation and Upgrade projects, appreciated for my work by customer as well as the team & Company. Created and presented an excellent image of the company and its services to customers, and coordinated and communicated well with clientele and management at all levels. Appreciations received from every customer he worked so for.